## **DILSHOD ADILBEKOV**

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

## CONTACTS

- **4** +996-558-586-801
- Telegram
- in Linkedin
- GitHub

## **SKILLS**

- Next.JS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- React
- CSS
- TailwindCSS
- Sass
- MaterialUI
- Ant design
- React-hook-from
- Redux
- Supabase
- Prisma
- Framer motion
- GSAP

### **LANGUAGES**

- English B1
- Russian B2
- Kyrgyz native
- Iranian B1

### **SUMMARY**

Enthusiastic and goal-oriented frontend developer with hands-on experience in creating responsive web applications. Experienced in working with modern frameworks and libraries like JavaScript, React, Next.js, TypeScript, Sass, and TailwindCSS. I am active in problem-solving, teamwork, and adaptability as well.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Junior Frontend Developer**

#### I Ant Studio

11.2024 -11.2024

- Developed the 'StrongPassword' Project A tool designed to help visitors check the security of their passwords.
- Designed a user-friendly interface with modern technologies, increasing user retention by 30%.
- Optimized usability, reducing password security check time by 40%.

**Tech Stack**: Next.JS , Typescript , TailwindCSS , MaterialUI , Ant Design, Zustand. Pixso.

# Junior Frontend Developer

# Motion Web It Academy

10.2024 -11.2024

- Participated in the development of "MovieStream," a movie platform that enhances user engagement by 25%.
- Improved performance, reducing loading times by 15%.
- Optimized usability, and increasing user retention by 20%

**Tech Stack**: Next.JS , Typescript , Sass , NextAuth , Ant Design, RTQ query , Zustand, Pixso.

# **Junior Frontend Developer**

### Motion Web It Academy

09Ю2024 -10.2024

Developed a responsive and user-friendly project, 'D-Tech,' enhancing UI usability by 50%.

- Increased performance, reducing loading times by 20%.
- Implemented scalable features that boosted user activity by 40%.

**Tech Stack**: Next.js, TypeScript, Sass, Prisma, Supabase, Ant Design, RTK Query, Zustand, Pixso.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Motion Web It Academy

2023 - 2024